let questions3 = [
    {
        question: "What is Global Warming?",
        option: [
            "Increasing temperature in Earth's atmosphere",
            "Decreasing temperature in a city",
            "Increasing rain rates in Earth",
            "Decreasing temperature rates",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Without the Greenhouse Effect the Earth would be too",
        option: [
            "warm",
            "cold",
            "dead",
            "normal",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is NOT an effect of Global Warming?",
        option: [            
            "Polar ice caps will melt.",
            "Coastal regions will be covered with rising sea levels.",
            "Some areas will experience serious droughts",
            "The Earth's rotation will slow down and eventually stop",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the mixture of gases surrounding the Earth called?",
        option: [            
            "carbon",
            "concentration",
            "atmosphere",
            "emissions",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "The main human activity that releases greenhouse gases is ?",
        option: [
            "using bottled water",
            "burning fossil fuels",
            "texting on cellphones",
            "eating meat",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Why are too many greenhouse gases bad for the environment? ",
        option: [
            "They cause trees to die.",
            "They release heat and will be the cause of the next ice age.",
            "They trap heat in our atmosphere causing the planet to warm up.",
            "They are fossil fuels which pollute our environment.",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a consequence of global warming? ",
        option: [
            "Seas rising (flooding)",
            "More severe storms and weather.",
            "Increased forest fires and drought.",
            "All of these",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these is the main source of carbon dioxide ?",
        option: [
            "Plants",
            "Burning fossil fuels",
            "Cows/agriculture",
            "Earth's soil",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            "TWhich of these is a main source of methane ?",
        option: [
            "Plants",
            "Burning fossil fuels",
            "Cows/agriculture",
            "Earth's soil",
    ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Gases in the atmosphere that trap heat are known as ?",
        option: [
            "Greenhouse Gas",
            "Global Warming",
            "Sunspot",
            "CFC's",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Why are forests important in reducing climate change?",
        option: [
            "use Carbon Dioxide to make food",
            "provide building materials",
            "are an important food source",
            "reflect all sunlight away from the Earth",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is contributing to an INCREASE in carbon dioxide in the atmosphere?",
        option: [
            "deforestation",
            "photosynthesis",
            "oceans",
            "all of the above",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which 2 greenhouse gases contribute the MOST to global warming of Earth?",
        option: [
            "N2O and H2O",
            "O3 and H2O",
            "CO2 and CH4",
            "H20 and O3",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "The main human activity that releases greenhouse gases is ?",
        option: [
            "using bottled water",
            "burning fossil fuels",
            "texting on cellphones",
            "eating meat",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Why is the increase of Greenhouse gasses a big issue?",
        option: [
            "It causes climate change and increase in the global temerature ",
            "It can lead to a major increase in Greenhouses ",
            "It leads to more factories",
            "It causes a major decrease in people",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "The greenhouse gas having the greatest role in human-caused global warming is ?",
        option: [
            "methane",
            "carbon dioxide",
            "CFCs (chlorofluorocarbons)",
            "ozone",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "How can global warming cause sea levels to rise? ",
        option: [
            "by causing it to rain more often",
            "by melting glaciers and ice caps",
            "by increasing the number of undersea volcanic eruptions",
            "by creating bigger and more powerful hurricanes",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Why does cutting down trees increase global warming?",
        option: [
            "trees soak up carbon dioxide",
            "trees provide shade which counteracts global warming",
            "trees absorbs the sun's energy without radiating back into the atmosphere",
            "trees drain greenhouse gases like methane from soil",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Things you can do to help decrease global warming include:",
        option: [
            "Eat more ice cream.",
            "Keep your freezer door open.",
            "Keep your air conditioner on high.",
            "Turn off your lights when youâ€™re not using them.",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "How are greenhouse gasses harming our environment?",
        option: [
            "They aren't",
            "Less heat is able to escape causing the Earth to cool down",
            "Less heat is able to escape causing the Earth to warm up",
            "More heat is able to escape",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following could increase the amount of greenhouse gasses in our atmosphere?",
        option: [
            "Burning fossil fuels",
            "Planting trees",
            "Walking to school and work",
            "All of these",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "As greenhouse gasses increase, what happens to heat flow out?",
        option: [
            "Increase",
            "Decrease",
            "Stays the Same",
            "No Trend",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What evidence is there to support that Global Warming is occurring?",
        option: [
            "Rising ocean temperatures",
            "Sea levels rising",
            "Increase in carbon dioxide in the atmosphere",
            "All of the above",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "If the Earth is like a greenhouse, carbon dioxide in the atmosphere is like ?",
        option: [
            "Plants",
            "Glass",
            "Sun",
            "Ground",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Why do we need greenhouse gasses?",
        option: [
            "We don't! All greenhouse gasses are bad",
            "They decrease Earth's temperature",
            "They help regulate Earth's climate",
            "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
];
